[Music]
life insurance products might prove a
better way to get insurance appreciated
as people feel that they are assuring
for more than risk to this end more
insurance companies are pushing for life
based settings polices the latest being
proceedings in dollars if the product
that will allow you our customers to
save for your children's education in
u.s. dollars for those that are in u.s.
dollars or those that want to save in
u.s. dollars this is intended to protect
the financial future of your loved ones
especially the children we have to cater
for for their education god forbid
something happens to you god forbid
that's a person permanent disability you
get 50% of the guaranteed amount we make
a guarantee to you that at the end of
the period you take a policy for five
ten fifteen years we make a guaranteed
payment to you we give you 50% of that
money right away right then at the end
of the period we pay hundred percent
along with any interest that has been
earned so the product satisfies not just
a hedge against currency devaluation or
inflation but it's basically a mode of
saving and adding protection onto it the
idea that you get an insurance policy
with a possibility that the insured risk
never actually comes to pass made
insurance less appealing but savings and
vehicles for instance life that give bad
dream value in cash to policyholders is
lending new impetus to insurance
penetration